<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: development | runningcode.io]]></title>
  <link href="http://runningcode.io/blog/categories/development/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://runningcode.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-05-14T16:19:24+03:00</updated>
  <id>http://runningcode.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[runningcode.io]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[distributed team]]></title>
    <link href="http://runningcode.io/2013/02/13/distributed-team/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-13T11:59:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://runningcode.io/2013/02/13/distributed-team</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A distruted team can be viewed as the necessary evil or the way of the future, or both, depending on where you are coming from. Essencially, for different reasons that we&rsquo;ll discuss later in this post, you sometimes find yourself in need of hiring people from across the globe, and working in a fast, dynamic, highly professional enviornment with a distributed team just complicated things farther.. or does is?</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>what is a distrubuted team?</h2>

<p>Wikipedia (that also calls this <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virtual_team">virtual team</a>) defines a distributed team as</p>

<blockquote><p>a group of individuals who work across time, space and organizational boundaries with links strengthened by webs of communication technology</p></blockquote>

<p>A while my friend @kesor tells me to never read the first line of wikipedia, I often find this first line to be summerizing the content wonderfully. Notice that there&rsquo;s no mentioning of the fact that the team is a development team, and that being distributed means organizational boundaries as well as space and time boundries.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s discuss those quialities.</p>

<h3>Space</h3>

<h3>Time</h3>

<h3>Organizational boundaries</h3>

<h2>when do you need to go distributed?</h2>

<h2>pros and cons</h2>

<h2>how do you manage a distributed team?</h2>

<h2>tools of the trade</h2>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
